Daddy is always busy.
爸爸总是很忙
He gets up at six o'clock
他早上六点起床
and goes to work after having breakfast.
吃完早饭后去工作
He is an amazing daddy.
他是个超棒的爸爸
The best in the world.
世界上最好的爸爸
I love him forever.
我永远爱他
I miss you already.
我已经开始想你了
I wish I saw you more.
我希望能更多的看到你
Daddy.
爸爸
Daddy, why do you have to be out so long?
爸爸   你为什么非要离开这么长时间呢
I miss you.
我想你
I love you.
我爱你
Oh, Olivia, I know.
哦   奥利维亚   我知道
I miss you, too.
我也想你
But I have to work to keep food on the table.
但我必须去工作来维持生活啊
I know. But why?
我知道   但是为什么呢
Honey, I wish I had more time with you. I really do.
亲爱的   我多希望能更多地和你在一起   我真的希望
But I want you to be happy.
但我想让你快乐
I wish you didn't have to go all the time.
我真希望你不必总是离开
Olivia, I know, honey.
奥利维亚   我知道   亲爱的